http://www.rotospa.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy - Rotospa - The Latest in Portable Spa TechnologyRotospa – The Latest in Portable Spa Technology
Trade Login
HelpCentre
RotoSpa Range
RotoSpa Hot Tubs
The DuoSpa S240The DuoSpa S080The QuatroSpaThe OrbisThe DuraSpa S160The DuraSpa S380
Download Operation ManualHelp CentreTrade Login
Customer ReviewsBlogContact UsDownload ManualDownload Brochure
RotoSpa Range
RotoSpa Hot Tubs
The DuoSpa S240The DuoSpa S080The QuatroSpaThe OrbisThe DuraSpa S160The DuraSpa S380
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how RotoSpa uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
RotoSpa is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
RotoSpa may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 June 2014.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Cookies
Our website does not use cookies. By using our website you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
Have a question?
0121 354 3428
| Site Map | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy |
Copyright ©2020 Rotospa
